Good, good, good.
Mr. Gao,
I'd like to propose a toast to you too.
Seeing you
dedicate yourself
to these art-loving kids,
I truly admire
your great compassion.
Let me make a promise
right here.
As long as you'll have me,
I, Feng Shu, am willing to follow you
for the rest of my life.
Really?
Of course it's true.
Mr. Meng,
see that?
He's taking advantage of the situation.
No.
He is completely sincere.
Feng Shu,
you really need to fix
that glib tongue of yours.
Mr. Mu just said it,
sincerity.
How was it?
You met with Yanyan, right?
I did.
But
Yanyan said she has a boyfriend
and warned me to stay away.
What boyfriend?
He's a good-for-nothing.
I've looked into him.
He's completely worthless.
If you're a real man,
you'll pursue her relentlessly.
I've got your back.
What are you afraid of?
Hearing you say that
puts my mind at ease.
Thank you, Mr. Gao.
No need to see me out.
Just enjoy your meal and drinks.
I'll take good care of Mr. Gao.
Is everything arranged?
Don't worry, Mr. Gao.
It's all been arranged.
My boss is going up soon.
Don't let him down.
I've given you everything
I was supposed to.
Rest assured.
At the time,
I followed Shen Xi's car
to the back gate
of the thermal power plant.
I was figuring out
where to intercept her and pull her over
pretending to be a traffic cop.
Then I saw
her hit someone.
Then why didn't you call the police
and an ambulance
immediately?
After all, a human life was at stake.
I was stunned
when I saw that person
get knocked so far away.
I was stunned
After I came to my senses,
I thought
Shen Xi was definitely
in trouble.
I figured
I could use the traffic cop identity
to help her clear the scene
and comfort her.
But
after the scene was cleared,
I was too embarrassed to ask
for her number.
So I made an excuse and slipped away.
According to Shen Xi's description,
you sounded quite convincing.
Did you study it specifically?
Not really.
Since I drive too,
I've paid attention
to their enforcement process.
Also, I got into
a minor accident once.
The other guy rear-ended me.
He bullied me for being a novice
and suggested settling it privately.
So we cleared the scene.
But afterwards,
he bit back
and claimed I rolled back into him.
If I remember correctly,
the officer handling the case
was this officer right here.
When was it?
About five or six years ago.
At that time,
my dad had just bought me a car.
Officer,
officer,
listen to me.
Why don't you go over there
and take a look?
It's a downhill slope.
He's a novice
driving a manual.
Rolling back is completely normal.
Nonsense!
I was driving perfectly fine.
You clearly lost control and hit me.
When you got out,
you even said you were distracted
because you argued with your wife.
Bro, how can you just make things up?
What does arguing with my wife
have to do with rolling back?
Rolling back?
I've been driving for so many years.
Would I roll back?
You have the nerve to say
I'm making things up?
You clearly rear-ended me.
You said you were in a hurry
and wanted to settle it privately.
And now you come here to call the police.
I see how it is now.
You're just bullying me because
I'm a newbie and don't know the rules.
You set me up on purpose.
Officer,
you have to believe me.
Why should they believe you?
Officer,
I'm a reporter.
You have to believe me.
What I'm saying is definitely the truth.
So what if you're a reporter?
Reporters have to speak the truth too.
What I'm saying is the truth.
You two,
look at
the gate.
This is the traffic police brigade,
not a wet market.
Go out the gate,
finish your argument, and then come back.
Okay, no.
Officer,
how about this...
Let's listen to the officer.
Okay.
You're the boss.
We'll listen to you.
Listen to me,
right?
Good.
I'll say this one last time.
According to the procedures
for handling road traffic accidents,
if the basic facts
of the accident cannot be
determined,
we will issue a road traffic
accident certificate to you.
You can apply for a review, mediation,
or file a civil lawsuit.
See? The officer says
it's equal responsibility.
Comrade.
Y-Yeah, I think so.
It's been too long.
I can't remember clearly.
N-Nothing.
Please continue.
So I thought,
if no one reported
Shen Xi's accident,
and I did it instead,
would it just
end up as equal liability?
But I was afraid
Shen Xi would call the police first,
so I decided
to clear the scene for her.
Then why did you turn yourself in?
I really didn't expect
my good intentions to make things worse.
It was just a traffic accident,
but my involvement
complicated things.
I saw everything.
You kept visiting Shen Xi,
almost driving her to depression.
She was dancing like crazy
on the balcony alone,
and even cried.
She cried? When?
Last time,
after you left.
This matter has indeed put
a lot of pressure on me.
Not to mention my car is
impounded by you guys,
even if I had one,
I wouldn't dare to drive.
Whether I'm sleeping or dancing,
I keep seeing that accident.
I keep seeing Mr. Gao
lunging at me covered in blood.
I'm really going crazy.
I can understand you.
It's inevitable for a girl
to have trauma after hitting
and killing someone
with a car.
If it's too much,
find a therapist to talk to.
Thank you,
Officer Jiang.
You're welcome.
We should be thanking you.
Thanks for the coffee.
So,
that Xiao Ze lives
right across from my place.
I really couldn't have imagined.
My every move
was actually being watched every day.
It's not exactly watching.
He just admires you,
appreciates you, and likes you.
Anyway, he-he-he's
not a pervert.
Ms. Shen,
this Xiao Ze,
he might just have
a weak sense of the law.
He doesn't have any bad intentions.
Including that day he followed you,
it was also to protect you.
He finally thought he had a chance
to bump into you.
Will he be sentenced?
That depends on
whether the procuratorate
decides to prosecute.
If they do,
it's up to the court
to decide the sentence.
We can't say for sure.
Please understand, okay?
Everyone,
based on our recent visits
and investigations...
Including the verification of surveillance
footage around the incident area
and the investigation into the
authenticity of the confession by Xiao Ze,
who turned himself in and impersonated
a traffic police officer.
At present, it can be confirmed
that there has been no contact
between Shen Xi and Xiao Ze.
Based on the testimonies of Shen Xi
and Xiao Ze,
as well as our investigation of the
accident scene,
we can basically reconstruct
the circumstances of Gao Yuhai's
fatal accident.
That day,
because his path was blocked by an
abandoned, unclaimed
old electric tricycle,
Gao Yuhai ran from the sidewalk
onto the motor vehicle lane.
That curve is a blind spot,
and coupled with the strong wind,
heavy rain,
and low visibility,
Shen Xi couldn't avoid him in time,
resulting in the accident
that caused Gao Yuhai's death.
Currently,
this is the result of our investigation.
Chief Wu.
Judging from these
investigation materials,
the main cause was Gao Yuhai's
sudden lane change,
which led to the accident.
Therefore, I believe
Gao Yuhai
bears the primary responsibility
for the accident.
Shen Xi, as the driver,
bears secondary responsibility
for the accident.
In addition,
since Gao Yuhai is deceased,
his only relative, Gao Yayan,
hopes to wrap things up quickly
to avoid public attention
and false rumors.
She has also applied
to drop the charges against Shen Xi.
So, Li,
your team
should impose administrative penalties
according to the law.
We can close the case now.
Got it.
So,
does anyone have any other thoughts?
Then
let's wrap things up
and close the case quickly.
This is
way too lavish
for a lunch.
Technically, as public servants...
Come on.
You ripped me off enough
when we were kids.
Stop pretending.
But that was when we were kids.
Besides, today I'm treating
my childhood friend Li Xingchen
and his friends.
Right. And most importantly,
I really need to treat
you three to a proper meal.
You've been working so hard
investigating my father's case lately.
Thank you.
Here, let me propose a toast.
Cheers.
You're too kind. It's just our job.
Thanks for your hard work, Captain Li.
It's nothing.
Please, sit.
Eat up. Aren't you hungry?
I am.
Yayan,
Have some shrimp.
Then I'll
try this first.
By the way,
what's the situation with Xiao Ze?
Him?
He's still in the detention center.
His family applied for bail.
But he'll definitely
face criminal liability.
Most likely, it'll be probation.
But
the final sentencing
will depend on the prosecutor
and the court.
Look at me, bringing this up again.
Let's drop it.
From today on,
we are all friends.
Right, let's not talk about that.
Let's have another toast.
Cheers.
Cheers!
Hello.
Please blow into this.
Stop!
After him!
Freeze!
What are you doing? Freeze!
Guilty conscience?
Why run?
It reeks of alcohol.
How much did you drink? Let's test it.
Take him away.
Thanks.
No problem.
Captain Li, what are you doing here?
I just finished dinner with some friends.
We'll get back to work then.
Good work.
Good work, everyone.
Just doing our job.
Enjoy your time off, Captain Li.
Not bad, Captain Li.
You've got some serious arm strength
after a full meal.
All right.
The 10.23 task force
is officially disbanded.
Hope we work together again.
Are you even a cop?
Who wishes for a task force
to reunite after disbanding?
Aren't you afraid
of having too many cases?
I sure am.
Yeah, Wei.
Don't jinx it like I do.
Knock on wood, quick.
Knock on wood.
Reuniting isn't impossible.
Like we could
grab a bite,
sing karaoke,
hang out,
watch a movie,
or have a few drinks.
You've got a lot of ideas.
Bye.
Take care. Good night. Bye.
Bye, Wei.
Bye.
Spit it out.
Say whatever is on your mind.
You caught me again.
I just wanted
to ask you a question.
But you don't have to answer
if you don't want to.
It's just...
your relationship with
your childhood friend Song Yanfei
isn't that simple, is it?
Not simple?
How is it not simple?
No, don't...
In what way?
Look at you, doing it again.
I said
you don't have to answer
if you don't want to.
Why are you getting worked up?
Am I getting worked up?
Are you done with your work?
Yes.
Are all the doubts cleared up?
Doubts?
What doubts are left?
Our task force is done with the work.
What else is there?
You can't tell?
You just can't see it.
Pighead.
Then... Captain Li,
what doubts are you talking about?
Tell me,
why did Feng Shu
report Song Yanfei with such certainty?
That's your doubt?
That's why I say
you two have an unusual relationship.
You're looking at this based on
personal feelings.
Look,
what's their relationship?
They're rivals in love.
What else would they do?
Isn't it just slinging mud
at each other?
Slinging it back and forth.
Just sling it first.
Just sling it first...
Hello,
hello.
Hello, Shen Xi.
It's Xiao Ze.
I've been released on bail.
I'd like to see you.
Is that okay?
Okay.
Welcome.
I'll get the door for you.
Xiao Ze,
have some water.
thank you for
what happened last time.
If you hadn't turned yourself in,
I probably couldn't have
explained it clearly,
let alone getting the car back.
No, no,
it was my fault.
If I hadn't caused trouble,
there probably
wouldn't have been so much mess.
It's my fault.
It's all my fault.
Shen Xi,
you have a really beautiful smile.
Xiao Ze,
have you eaten?
Let me treat you to a meal.
Okay,
but it's my treat.
What do you want to eat?
Hotpot.
I know a really good place.
I'll take you there.
Let's take my car.
Where are we going today?
That place is too low.
This place is out of reach.
Let's just go to our usual spot.
Starring (in order of the number
of strokes in their surnames)
Li Xingchen, Yu Xiaotong
Shen Xi, Xie Tiantian
Special Appearance (in order of
the number of strokes in their surnames)
Xiao Ze, Wang Hao
Feng Shuwen
Jiang Dahai, Liu Zheting (Liu Zheting)
Li Xintong
Cast (in order of the number
of strokes in their surnames)
Forensic Doctor Cheng Gong
Li Xingchen's Classmate Liu Haohan
Zhao Wenjuan, Li Ziying
Young Song Yanfei, Chen Nuoyan
Investor
Zha Minxin
Xiao Ze's Mother Zhao Yue'en
Assistant Bai Zhihao
Xu Jiayue
Zhao Wenjuan, Li Ziying
Special Guest Classmate Yue Yue
Yao Sha
Li Xingchen's Classmate Tang Tang,
Dai Guoming
Woman Sun Meili
Driver Wang Yiguo, Liang Hui
Liu Ran
Waiter Liu Jiaqi, Dai Guoming
Daughter Zhang Qiying
College Student
Surveillance Police Officer Qin Zhiqiang
Xiao Ze's Mother Pei Xiao
Stagehand Xiao Zhang, Li
Young Man Tang Yuye
Police Colleague Li Lijun
Female Secretary Qian Duoduo
Mr. Zhao, Liu Junjie
Wounded Person Xu Ganggang
Scrapyard Boss Zhang, Li Chenghu
Female Teacher Ai Li
Company Manager Bai Yongjun
Woman Liu Yutong
Wu Zeyu
Female Nurse Bai Wanting
Guo Xinye
Speaker Nan Xi, Xu Ziyi
Man in Black Speaker Zhu Yiqi
Bai Xiaosi's Stand-in Zhao Peng
Taxi Driver Bai Lei
Yan Yongmei
Actor Hu Zexuan
Cleaner Liu Li
Crew
Chief Presenter Xu Yue
Hai Ziqing
Co-Presenters Feng Fei, Guo Zhiyuan
Guo Guo
Chief Planner Li Meina
Chief Distributor Hu Kaichen
Police Consultant / Original Story Fu Jun
Production Team
Chief Producer
Producer
Production Manager
Daily Life Producer Yin Zhongheng
Stage Management Team
Yang Qunbao
Kitchen
Kitchen Manager Yin Xiumei
Li Zhiwei, Ma Yuan
Hu Lei, Qiao Xueyue
Zhang Haiping, Cao Yongjie
Screenwriter Yue Shunming
Executive Director Sui Chenggong
Script Supervisor Li Ting
On-site Assistant Director Liu Haohan
Pre-production Audio Equipment Provided by
Beijing Wenhui Qiming Culture Communication Co., Ltd.
Sound Assistants Wu Yingxue, Zhang Qichun
Props Art: Zhang Xueqi
Head of Props
On-Set Assistant: Li
Camera Department
Director of Photography: Li Yixu
A-Camera Assistant
B-Camera Assistant: Cao Xing
C-Camera Operator: Ma Mingguo
Aerial Photographer: Zhan Yuchen
Behind the Scenes: Li Chen
Lighting Department
Lighting Director: Gao Yun
Te Rigun
Styling Department
Head of Wardrobe & Makeup: Ma Yi
Hair & Makeup: Yuan Zihan, Wang Peng
On-Set Hair & Makeup: Liu Lu, Guo Xinye
On-Set Wardrobe Supervisor:
Zhang Lei, Yi Junli
Beijing Very Cola Culture Media Co., Ltd.
Marketing Director: Li Yiyi
Project Coordinator: Zhao Zihan
Graphic Design: Ren Zhongjun, Shi Qi
Post-Production
Colorist: Niu Xuerui
Subtitles: Su
Ambience Editor: Zhang Xinyu
VFX Production
Production Supervisor: Gao Dong
VFX Executive: Jin Linxin
Shang Chenyao
Music Production
Music Director: Xiao Zhuang
Score Production: Xiao Zhuang, Wang Daifu
Music Coordinator: Jiang Zheng, Liu Zining
Guitar: Liu Zining
Cello: Zi Long
Score Mixing: Zhao Yi
Vocal Recording: Zheng Suyang
"Brothers"
Composer: Xiao
Producer: Xiao Zhuang
"Song of Spring"
Children's Vocals: Zhang Maolin
Lyricist: Yue Shunming
Arranger: Xiao Zhuang
Producer: Xiao Zhuang
"Promise"
Lyricist: Bai Yuxiang
Producer: Xiao Zhuang
Gao Jingman
Composer: Xu Yue
Composer: Xu
Producer: Xu Yue
"Half a Beat Slow"
Vocals: Xu Yue
Fan Fan
Lyricist: Bai Yuxiang
"Only You" (Russian)
Publicity Department
of Shiyan Municipal Party Committee
Shiyan Public Security Bureau
Wujia Catering Management
Service Co., Ltd.
Shiyan Hengjiu Kanghua Real Estate
Co., Ltd. (Longcheng Mansion)
Hubei Zesheng Property Service Co., Ltd.
No. 88 Gongyuan Road,
Zhangwan District, Shiyan City
Exclusive Social Media Platform
Chief Partner Media
Co-Production Company
Xichengyi Film and Television
Media Co., Ltd.